

### **Summary**

Passionate and well-qualified mobile engineer with more than 3 years of experience. Working with Android and Flutter. Studying Agile, Clean Architecture, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares.

## Favorite technologies



# **Employment history**

Mobile developer at Megaleios June 2021 - August 2021

Mobile developer at Bean Softwares
March 2021 - June 2021

Mobile developer at Thalamus Digital July 2020 - June 2021

Mobile developer at MFIT Personal January 2020 - May 2020

#### Education

Computer Science at Univali February 2020 - Present

English at KNN Idiomas September 2020 - Present

## **Projects**

Pokédex: coding challenge August 2021 - August 2021 Android tech challenge for a position at B2W.

Pineapple: budget planner August 2021 - Present

A personal budget planner

iCut: online barbershops

May 2021 - Present

A barber appointment app

StudentPlus: study planner August 2018 - April 2021

A study planner based on the Pomodoro technique.

#### **Details**

Itajaí, SC, Brazil contact@lucasbatista.me

### Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp

Website

### **Skills**

TDD

Refactoring

Clean Architecture

SOLID

Design Patterns

DevOps

UML

# Languages

English

Agile

#### **Hobbies**

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.